## Inayat Ullah

AREAS OF EXPERTISE

PHP Laravel Framework

React JS

Redux & Redux saga

SQL skills

PERSONAL SKILLS

Attention to detail

Good analytical skills

Goals orientated

PERSONAL DETAILS

Al Ameen Housing Society Near, Lahore DHA Phase 5 E: inayatullahkks@gmail.com

G: https://github.com/inaat

*M*: +923428927305

DOB: 04/11/1998

Nationality: Pakistani

PERSONAL SUMMARY

A highly resourceful, innovative, and competent Laravel developer with extensive experience in the database design and coding of websites specifically in Laravel and React Js. Possessing considerable knowledge of the development of web applications and scripts using PHP programming language and JavaScript.

**WORK EXPERIENCE** 

INJAZAT SOFTWARE (Saudi Arabia), (Remotely)
LARAVEL AND REACT DEVLOPER December 2020 - Present

Responsible for the technical and administration aspects of the companies React Js. Also the first point of call for providing technical support as well as specialist technical input.

Duties:

- Develop custom API layer to handle all CRUD transactions, JWT token management and implemented interceptors to embed custom headers.
- To Manage Redux-Saga with Immutable Js

SKYLINE WEB SOLUTION (Local)

LARAVEL DEVELOPER

June 2019 – November 2020

## KEY SKILLS AND COMPETENCIES

- Able to plan the structure of a database
- Ability to multi-task, react quickly to shifting priorities and meet deadlines.
- Continuously monitoring industry trends, technologies and standards.
- Excellent attention to detail both front and back end.
- Solid web development experience using OOP, PHP, LARAVEL, PYTHON, MySQL, JavaScript,, HTML and CSS.

## ACADEMIC QUALIFICATIONS

BS Software Engineering Lahore Leads University 2017 – jan-2021

FSC: Pre Engineering
GHSS khwazakhela Swat 2014 - 2016